It only took half an hour to build an Agent Teams monitoring panel using K2.5. Didn't I share a lot of insights about Agent Teams the other day?
Insights about agent teams
I noticed many friends in the comment section have already put it into practice,
especially many friends without technical backgrounds.
Agent Teams has opened the door to AI for ordinary people.
I think that simply acquiring information doesn't really change oneself.
But if the information drives us to take action,
Practice yields results.
Then a small positive feedback loop is formed and sustained.
These gains will increase incrementally.
On your AI journey,
I have several previous videos that should be able to motivate people to take action.
For example, how to obtain information sources,
how to ignite our talent for building toolchains,
how to build a skill effectively
How to effectively use Agent Teams.
So today I'm going to share exactly how all these pieces come together.
If you happen to have watched my previous content,
you will understand what a small closed-loop process looks like when I solve a problem.
From 'watch and leave' to 'see and do'
Let's go back to the pain point I mentioned in my previous video,
Agent Teams is a black box,
It still requires trying many orchestration combinations to test its effectiveness.
However, there is an issue.
I found that the communication between team members is not transparent,
All we can see is just a title,
and the communication information is all mixed in the Messages of Claude Code,
if it gets compressed,
it's completely invisible.
A few days ago, I saw a post shared by an expert on X,
Claude Code was reverse engineered,
He discovered that agents communicate by reading and writing JSON files.
This article should be from a senior member of the dify team.
This post mainly discusses some technical details about Agent Teams discovered by the expert.
The technical details about Agent Teams discovered by the expert
But to put it simply, the details of Agent Teams are all stored under this directory.
I have to say,
Nowadays, such substantive content is becoming increasingly rare on X.
Moreover, a new trend is increasingly emerging,
using AI to continuously amplify emotionally charged correctness,
but also articles that fool the gullible.
So I'm adding one principle for filtering information sources,
that is, what kind of content can make you take immediate action,
That is meaningful content.
I fed the expert's post to the AI.
I fed the post to AI to verify if it's true, and I asked him,
Can you verify for me whether what he said is true or not?
I used Kimii K2.5,
It didn't take him much time,
The verification was quickly completed,
The verification result is precisely in this context. I used K2.5, and it was successfully verified very quickly.
And this context became the foundation for our second step.
We need to turn it into a tool.
I asked if it could create a beautiful frontend and backend web panel based on the Node tech stack,
a beautiful web panel with both frontend and backend
allowing me to monitor the log files generated by these Agent Teams at any time
Moreover, using Agent Teams to implement K2.5 was completed quickly.
Of course, this wasn't completed in one shot
I made about two rounds of iterations through the context window,
Finally, I came up with a version that I'm quite satisfied with.
I have previously shared how to use Chrome DevTools in conjunction with K2.5's multimodal capabilities
How to use Chrome DevTools with K2.5's multimodal
basically achieve
I just need to say what I'm not satisfied with,
it can optimize according to my direction.
Then the third step is my frequently used Skill Creator,
I used Skill Creator to encapsulate this frontend and backend project into a skill.
Next time, simply enter the command /teams-dashboard to launch both the frontend and backend.
slash team dashboard can start both the frontend and backend
Open the webpage
See how convenient it is, let me demonstrate for you.
I currently have these teams and a dashboard,
As you can see, this is how it looks when opened
The left column here displays the teams you have previously created.
On the right side is the inbox of the team members.
for example, the leader,
some status updates and task logs he sent,
Of course, there might still be some bugs,
but I think it's pretty much there,
It's ready to use.
That's it for now,
I only spent half an hour,
turned a post into a part of my productivity toolchain.
This entire process is just a small part of my daily work routine.
What I want to share with everyone is,
This is a world of compound interest.
When you spend time reading a piece of information,
so you can take action,
digest some information.
Whether you've learned Knowledge,
or turned into your own toolchain,
These have all become assets capable of generating compound interest.
So if you ask me what makes a good source of information,
Whether it can generate compound interest is a great criterion.
If you often watch my videos,
you'll find that the content I share is actually systematic,
are all skill sets.
So if the content of this episode has also motivated you to take action,
You might as well revisit previous episodes and put them into practice,
It will definitely be better.
Additionally, I believe that merely reaching out for help may not lead to growth,
Finally, while I was writing this draft.
It's more convenient to trace past chat records, and I've identified another pain point,
I wanted to use the resume command in Claude Code to restore the session,
Then I recorded a video to share the previous conversation with everyone.
But I found that once the context was compressed,
the session is also incomplete, making it more convenient to trace back past chat records.
So while I was drafting the script, I had the AI create a session-dashboard skill for me by referencing the teams-dashboard.
created a session dashboard for me
Now I can more easily trace back past chat records.
How about it?
Did you learn it? That's all for this episode.
Alright,
That's all for this episode.
Thank you everyone.